Kimberly King

Customer Service/ Part Sales

Gibbstown, NJ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Kimberly-King/7367be18ff88447c

Experienced in all areas of Administrative Support and Inside

Sales/Customer service with 15 years of proven success. Very organized, competent and works effectively on a team as well as independently. Ability to quickly assess customer needs, expedite service, displaying effective quality resolution with a committed focus on customer satisfaction.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Service/ Part Sales

Niehoff Endex - Swedesboro, NJ - May 2011 to Present

Enters purchase order from fax, email, phone

Give Quotations

Direct Sales

Researches parts from engineer prints,

Buyer

Places Purchase Orders with Vendors

Forecast parts in Inventory

Returns, Credits

Knowledge of pricing and discounts

Billing and invoicing on a weekly basis

Creates UPS and Federal Express labels

Weekly report of shipments we get in for the prior week

Send purchase order to vendors and confirmations

Call Center /Customer Service Rep/Temporary Position

EMD Chemicals - Gibbstown, NJ - February 2010 to March 2011

Manage fast-pace multi-task order entry

Manage incoming calls /queue from customers and end users 40-75 daily

Order processing from phone, email, edi, web, and intramal

Relate with internal cross functional teams to achieve goals

Provide on time order acknowledgement/confirmation to the customers with updated information

Customer Service Representative

VWR International - Bridgeport, NJ - May 2006 to February 2009

Received an average of 40-100 customer calls daily in a call center

Processes orders via phone, email, and fax

Handles customer complaints (return, credits, claims, and dangerous goods

Researches products by calling vendors to obtain additional information

Solves problems for customer by stock checking, trouble shooting, and technical support inquires

Quotes pricing to customers by via phone or fax

Tracking orders and shipments

Worked very close with the Sales Representatives

Searched internet for products

Paulsboro High School.

Computer Literate - Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, and Outlook) Lotus, VBQ, ESS, AS400, Sap, Max and Internet experience.

EDUCATION

Paulsboro High School